

Contact

+8801838652572

P Bhulta, Rupgonj, Narayangonj

Education

2018-2021

BA in English

Victoria University of Bangladesh

2015-2017

Higher Secondary Certificate

Bhulta High School and Collage

Skills

HTML CSS

Javascript Bootstrap

Tailwind CSS React js

Next is Node is

Typescript Python

Php Express js

Mongodb Mysql

Docker Kubernetes

Linux Jenkins

Ansible AWS EC2

Languages

Bangla Native

English Communicational

Shohel Mia

Full Stack Developer

Protfolio Link: https://glassmorphism-protfolio.vercel.app/

About

I am selftaught full stack web developer. I love new technology to learn and implement in projects. I have clear knowledge of software developement life cycle. I have working experience on both frontend and backend also some devops tools like Docker, Kubernetes, Jenkins, Ansible, AWS EC2, AWS EKS and Linux. I can implement project into CI/CD pipeline. Primarily, I work on Javasctipt but have basic knowledge on several programing languages like Python and Php.

Working Experience

Facebook Clone - Full-Stack Developer

January 2022 - Fabruary 2022

- Creating UI like facebook and secure API.
- Hosting in heroku hosting platform.
- Creating docker images and push dockerhub.
- Creating container orchestration or kubernetes cluster.
- Implement CI/CD pipeline using jenkins.

Link: https://facebookclon.herokuapp.com/

Flipkart Clone - Full-Stack Developer

December 2021 - January 2022

- Creating UI like Flipkart and anmin dashboard.
- Creating sucure API using json web token.
- Hosting in heroku hosting platform.
- Creating docker images and push dockerhub.

Link: https://saykotflipkart.herokuapp.com/

Link: https://saykotflipkartadmin.herokuapp.com/

Blog App - Full-Stack Developer

August 2021 - August 2021

- Creating nice loking and responsive UI and secure API.
- Hosting in heroku hosting platform.
- Creating docker images and push dockerhub.
- Creating container orchestration or kubernetes cluster.
- Implement CI/CD pipeline using jenkins.

Link: https://saykotblog.herokuapp.com/